



asthajain497@gmail.com



939949204



linkedin.com/in/astha-jain-881399201



github.com/asthajain08

SKILLS

Digital Marketing

Marketing

Social Media marketing

Leadership & management

Public Speaking



Python

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

Node.js

React.js

DSA

Canva

SCSS

UI/UX

CERTIFICATES

TCS NQT-IT (07/2023)
TCS NOT score card

Programing With Java By NPTEL

Cloud Application Development By IBMCE

ASTHA JAIN

I'm an enthusiastic, responsible and hard working person. Being worked for different projects helped me to adopt to the changes quickly and made me a mature team worker. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using own initiative. I am able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Social Media Manager

Teerthanker Mahaveer University

08/2023 - Present Moradabad

Tasks

- I plan and execute content strategies, manage platforms, and engage with the audience to boost the online presence.
- I track analytics to optimize campaigns and ensure alignment with brand objectives.

Manager

Firstcry.com

10/2020 - Present Gwalior

Tasks

- I have accelerated sales by implementing customer-centric strategies, optimizing inventory, and enhancing in-store experiences.
- I have maintained high operational standards, fostering team efficiency and ensuring consistent customer satisfaction.

Web Developer

Teerthanker Mahaveer University

07/2023 - 08/2023 Moradabad

Tasks

- I made college websites, making them user-friendly and informative.
- I used HTML,CSS and JavaScript, node.js, react.js, php, SCSS and mongodb for the websites

Frontened developer

All Softsolutions

06/2022 - 08/2022 Chandigarh

Tasks

I worked on front-end development tasks, including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript coding, to ensure the websites are visually appealing, responsive, and user-friendly.

Data Science using Python

Verzeo

06/2021 - 07/2021 Bangalore

Tasks

- I worked on data science projects, where I used machine learning models, and implement data visualization techniques.
- I use Python libraries like NumPy, Pandas, and Scikit-learn to perform statistical analysis, build predictive models, and evaluate their performance.

CERTIFICATES

Python for Data Science

By cognitiveclass.ai by IBM

Big data engineer By IBMCE

Docker Essential:A developer introduction

By IBMCE

Introduction to python By IBMCE

Advance RDBMS
By IBMCE

Spring Framework
By IBMCE

EDUCATION

B.Tech CSE ADCA in collabration with IBM

Teerthanker Mahaveer University

2020 - Present Moradabad

Marks

80%

12th

Gwalior Glory High School

2019 - Present Gwalior

Marks

80%

10th

Carmel Convent School

2017 - 2018 Gwalior

Marks

65%

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Nursing college(TPCON) website (07/2023 - 08/2023)

- This project aimed to provide a modern, user-friendly, and informative online platform for students, faculty, and visitors to engage with the college's offerings and resources.
- Made for Teerthanker Mahaveer University. I have used HTML, CSS, Scss, mode.js, react.js and JavaScript
- Link: tpcon.tmu.ac.in

Education college(TMIMT BTC) website (07/2023 - 08/2023)

- This project aimed to provide a modern, user-friendly, and informative online platform for students, faculty, and visitors to engage with the college's offerings and resources.
- Made for Teerthanker Mahaveer University. I have used HTML, CSS, Scss, mode.js, react.js and JavaScript.
- Link: tmimtbtc.tmu.ac.in

Quickmeet webiste (04/2023 - 06/2023)

- It have a break functionality, conveys admin for a break without disrupting the meeting. User chats i.e., meeting 'chat and dashboard's chat are synced. Users can send/ receive messages from the meet/dashboard both.
- □ I have used Socket Io, WebRTC, Firebase (for Database), Node, express JS (Server)HTML, CSS.

File sharing website (03/2023 - 05/2023)

- This project uses JavaScript, Node.js and Mongo DB it allows users to securely upload, store, and share files with others.
- The project typically includes implementing user registration and authentication functionality, allowing users to create accounts, log in, and maintain their own file repositories.

Whatsapp chat data anyalysis (10/2022 - 11/2022)

- This project aim to develop a complete interface where users can upload the WhatsApp chat in text. It will provide users to study the chats, get the report with interactive graphs.
- I use Python libraries like NumPy, Pandas, and Scikit-learn .And used stremlite for building interactive web application.

Diabetes prediction (06/2021 - 07/2021)

- This project provides an opportunity to apply machine learning techniques to a real-world healthcare problem and aims to identify potential risk factors for diabetes.
- I use Python libraries like NumPy, Pandas, and Scikit-learn to perform statistical analysis, build predictive models, and evaluate their performance.

Weather forecast website (04/2022 - 05/2022)

- It provides up-to-date and accurate information about the current weather conditions and forecasts for future days. It gives details such as temperature, humidity, wind speed, precipitation, and visibility.
- I have used HTML, CSS and JavaScript